[{"id": 2851, "question": "Daniel Brown was just five years old when he climbed into the family car and let it roll away down the road. He was only three when he flooded the kitchen. His mother, Angela Brown is very busy looking after her new baby, a little girl called Laura, as well as Daniel. She told us, \"Daniel is so full of curiosity .\" At that moment, we hear a loud noise and then silence. We go upstairs and find Daniel getting out of a wardrobe which he has pulled over onto the floor, with a book in his hand. \"It's for you, Mum,\" he says and looks up at his mum and smiles. Seven-year-old Daniel has a lovely face. He has golden hair, big brown eyes, and a friendly smile. I have to admit that Daniel doesn't look like a naughty boy. Angela told me all about it, \"Once I found him as he was about to put Jasper in ...\n\nQ: What does \"the most expensive crime\" refer to?", "options": ["Daniel flooded the kitchen and it destroyed the carpet.", "Daniel pulled over a wardrobe onto the floor and it broke into pieces.", "The family car was damaged because Daniel let it roll away down the road.", "Their dog was killed because Daniel put it in the washing machine."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 605, "question": "No matter where he lives, 16-year-old Danny Lopez feels like an outsider: he is half-Mexican and half-white. At his private high school in wealthy northern San Diego, California, US, Lopez is too brown to fit in, whereas for the Mexican side of his family in National City, just a dozen miles from the border, he is too white to belong. Different from both sides, Lopez is silent in school. He focuses on his passion for baseball and working hard to improve the pitches that have kept him off the school team. Mexican Whiteboy, by Matt de la Pena, is about a teenager's search for identity. It was named as one of the Top Ten Best Books for Young Adults in 2009 by the US Young Adult Library Services Association. When Lopez's mother decides to go to live with her wealthy white boyfriend in San Fran...\n\nQ: Most probably \"Mexican Whiteboy\" is a   _  .", "options": ["book", "club", "newspaper", "organization"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1009, "question": "After the first World War, a small group of veterans returned to their village in Britain. Most of them managed to get along fairly well, but one--Francis Blustering, who had been wounded and who never recovered his strength-- was unable to work like others. In time he became very poor. Yet he was too proud to accept anything from the people in the village. Once, these veterans held a reunion dinner in the home of Jules Grandin, who had made a good deal of money. Grandin produced a curiosity --a large old gold coin. Each man examined it with interest as it passed around the long table. All, however, had drunk wine freely and the room was full of noisy talk, so that the gold piece was soon forgotten. Later, when Grandin remembered it and asked for it, the coin was missing. One of them sugge...\n\nQ: Francis Blustering lived a poor life because   _  .", "options": ["he was badly wounded in the battle", "he was unable to work like ordinary people", "he was too proud to get on well with other people", "he was waiting for his chance"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3240, "question": "NEW YORK--Microsoft on Monday made another effort to challenge Apple's iPhone and Google's Android in the exploding smartphone market--launching a wireless operating system,Windows Phone 7. Consumers will consider it\"always delightful and thoroughly mine,\"Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer said at a launch event. Ballmer said last year that Microsoft had\" _ \"with its Windows Mobile operating system.For example,it failed to keep up with touch-screen innovations that make iPhones and Android phones easy to use. Microsoft fell from third to fourth place in market share this year,behind BlackBerry,iPhone and Android. Only 10.8% of smartphone owners used Microsoft's system in August,down from 18% last December. But Windows Phone 7 is\"a total departure from anything they've done\".Microsoft says it soug...\n\nQ: Why did Microsoft see a drop in market share last year?", "options": ["Because its operating system didn't catch up with changes.", "Because its phones can't show videos from YouTube.", "Because it was inconvenient to take photos using its phones.", "Because its system was based only on Microsoft soft wares."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1145, "question": "Thousands of people living in the Chinese capital will celebrate the start of the Chinese New year by heading for the ski resorts . Never mind that Beijing's dry weather seldom produces snow. It is cold enough in winter for snow-making machines to make a covering for the hills north to the capital. And the rapid growth of a pleasure-seeking middle class has formed the basis for this new craze . Since Beijing's first ski resort was opened ten years ago, the sport has enjoyed astonishing increase. There are now more than a dozen resorts. Clothes markets in the city have added bright colored ski suits to their winter collections. Mr. Wei, a manager of a newly-opened ski resort in Beijing, sees the growth of an industry that could soon lead Chinese to head for the ski resorts of Europe. In rec...\n\nQ: What does this text mainly talk about?", "options": ["Convenience for skiers brought about by private cars.", "Skiing as a new way of enjoying one's spare time.", "Things to be considered when starting a ski resort.", "A sudden increase of ski training classes in Beijing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2653, "question": "Kabul,Oct.28 (Xinhuanet)--- Unknown armed men in military uniform kidnapped three staff of the United Nations in the Afghan capital city at broad daylight Thursday ,Afghan officials confirmed . \"Three armed men in military uniform _ a UN car in Baraki area ofprefix = st1 /Kabulcity early afternoon and took away three persons including two women with them, \"Rohullah, a witness at the site told Xinhua. The kidnappers also badly beat up the Afghan driver of the UN car, added Rohullah who is a lorry driver in the city. The area has been watched over by UN guards. UN officials as well as Afghan confirmed the incident but refused to provide further information. The three kidnapped , according to some officials , who are from Britain, Ireland and Kosovo, were working for the UN-sponsored Joint El...\n\nQ: What happened when the kidnapping took place?", "options": ["A lorry driver was badly beaten up", "three men and two women were taken away", "No one else witnessed the sudden kidnapping", "Two women together with one man was kidnapped"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 901, "question": "\"Mommy, I'm a funny bird,\" Jack, my almost-4-year-old tells me. He moves his little fingers like wings. \"You are?\" I say. I'm sitting across from him while he eats breakfast at our table. I smile; he says the greatest things. A week ago, however, when he had chocolate on his face and I licked my finger to wipe it off, he said, \"Don't put your dirty water on me.\" A week ago, I wouldn't have been sitting here with him during breakfast. I wouldn't have been up, emptying the dishwasher, cleaning the kitchen, or answering emails. We always had dinner together at the table, but other meals got much less attention. I work from home, and my husband owns an advertising agency and often travels. We were so busy that we had to do the chores during breakfast or lunch. Why was I not sitting down with m...\n\nQ: After visiting the friends, the author   _  .", "options": ["was determined to learn to cook", "asked her husband to have every meal with her", "decided to have dinner together with her family", "was advised by her husband to learn from the friends"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 906, "question": "Under new rules posted by the Civil Aviation administration of China on Friday, pilots will have to pass a \"level four\" test of Mandarin Chinese, China's official language. Those who speak with an accent that \"often impedes\" comprehension will not pass. These rules take effect in January 2016. China's 56 ethnic groups speak more than 80 languages and dialects. Even native Mandarin speakers can have trouble communicating with each other depending on the strength of their accents, which can be mutually unintelligible . One flight trainer illustrated the scope for linguistic confusion, especially when common English aviation terms are used. Asked if there is a problem on board, a Chinese pilot might answer in the negative with the words mei you, or \"there isn't. But someone speaking with a he...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Sichuan dialect has the contrary meaning to Mandarin.", "Native Mandarin speakers can understand each other well.", "It isn't necessary for a pilot to pass the test before January 2016.", "\"May day\" is a distress call in our everyday life."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 233, "question": "Nothing is more frustrating than not being able to sleep, tossing and turning . Your mind is racing, going over everything that happened that day. Night noises keep you awake. What can you do? Here are some things you can do to help you to fall asleep. Sleep only when sleepy This reduces the time you are awake in bed. If you can't fall asleep within 20 minutes, get up and do something boring until you feel sleepy. Don't expose yourself to bright light while you are up. The light tells your brain that it is time to wake up. Don't take naps This will ensure that you are tired at bedtime. If you just can't make it through the day without a nap, sleep less than one hour, and take a nap before 3 p.m. Get up and go to bed at the same time every day Even on weekends! When your sleep cycle has a r...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["A regular sleep cycle will make you feel better.", "Taking exercise now and then can help you sleep well.", "Have a little food when you feel very hungry before bedtime.", "The drop in your body temperature makes you feel sleepy."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 62, "question": "Nelson Mandela was a figure of international fame, and many details of his life and career were public knowledge. But here are four things you may not have known about the late South African leader. 1. He was a boxing fan. In his youth, Nelson Mandela enjoyed boxing and long-distance running. Even during the 27 years he spent in prison, he would exercise every morning. \"I did not enjoy the violence of boxing so much as the science of it. I was curious by how one moved one's body to protect oneself, how one used a strategy both to attack and retreat, how one paced oneself over a match,\" he wrote in his autobiography Long Walk to Freedom. 2. His original name was not Nelson. Rolihlahla Mandela was nine years old when a teacher at the primary Methodist school where he was studying in Qunu, So...\n\nQ: What happened to Mandela when he was about to give the speech?", "options": ["He broke his glasses into pieces.", "He had to use his wife's glasses.", "He left his own glasses at home.", "His wife wanted to borrow his glasses."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1881, "question": "The man from the west stopped and drew back his arm. \"You're not Jimmy Wells,\" he said in a quick and angry way, \"Twenty years is a long time, but not long enough to change a man' nose from a Roman to pug.\" \"It sometimes changes a good man into a bad one,\" said the tall man, \"you've been under arrest for ten minutes. Silky Bob. prefix = st1 /Chicagothinks you may have dropped over our way and phones us she wants to have a word with you. Going quietly, are you? That's sensible. Now before we go to the station here's a note I was asked to hand you. You may read it here at the window. It's from Patrolman Wells.?\" The man from the West opened the little piece of paper handed him. His hand was steady when he began to read, but it trembled a little by the time he finished. The note was rather sh...\n\nQ: The man from the West must have broken the law   _  .", "options": ["in Chicago", "inNew York", "in his hometown", "somewhere else"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3024, "question": "For years we have been dieting strictly after the year-end overeating, afraid that when summer. comes, the bigger size we have accumulated will betray how we ate. Now scientists say, it's a little bug that causes obesity . As the holiday season with its abundant feasting arrives, millions of food lovers are keeping an eye on their figures. But scientists have found that weight gain is not about too much Christmas turkey or hot chocolates, but some bacteria in your guts . Chinese scientists recently discovered a type ofbacteria in guts that may be to blame for obesity. A research team led by Zhao Liping, a professor in Shanghai, has identified a precise link between a particular kind ofbacteria and unusual weight gain. \"The endotoxin released by the bacterium can activate a gene that helps ...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?", "options": ["People's eating habits.", "Healthy lifestyles.", "A medical discovery.", "The consequence of obesity."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 438, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: Mr. Torres became blind when  _  .", "options": ["his daughter was just born", "he was thirteen years old", "his mother died of cancer", "his wife was out of work"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1293, "question": "In many countries today, laws protect wildlife. In India the need for such protection was realized centuries ago. About 300 B.C. an Indian writer described forests that were somewhat like national parks today. The killing of game animals was carefully governed. Some animals were fully protected. Within the forest, nobody was allowed to cut trees, burn wood, or trap animals for their furs. Animals that became dangerous to human visitors were trapped or killed outside the park, so that other animals would not become uneasy. The need for wildlife protection is greater now than ever before. About a thousand sorts of animals are in danger of extinction, and the speed at which they are being destroyed has been putting on. With mammals, for example, the speed of extinction is now about one sort e...\n\nQ: The report says that in Indian forests of long ago  _  .", "options": ["hunters were given permits to hunt game", "only dangerous animals were to be killed", "the killing of game animals was controlled", "no killing of animals was allowed"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1552, "question": "City Varieties The Headrow, Leeds. Tel. 430808 Oct 10-11 only A Night at the Varieties.All the fun of an old music hall with Barry Cryer, Duggle Brown, 6 dancers, Mystina, Jon Barker, Anne Dural and the Tony Harrison Trio. Laugh again at the old jokes and listen to your favourite songs. Performances: 8 pm nightly. Admission: L5; under 16 or over 60: L4. York Theatre Royal prefix = st1 /St Leonard's Place, York. Tel. 223568 Sept 23- Oct 17 Groping for Words-- a comedy by Sue Townsend. Best known for her Adrian Mole Diaries, Townsend now writes about an evening class, which two men and a woman attend. A gentle comedy. Admission: First night, Mon: L2; Tues- Fri: L3.25 - 5.50; Sat: L3.50 - 5.75. Halifax Playhouse King's Cross Street, Halifax. Tel. 365998 Oct 10-17 On Golden Pondby Ernest Thomp...\n\nQ: If you want to see a play with old jokes and songs, which phone number will you ring to book a seat?", "options": ["502116", "223568", "365998", "430808"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1906, "question": "If you want to live longer and lower the risk of heart disease, a move to the mountains may help. Research by scientists in Greece shows that living in the mountains is good for the heart and longevity . People living at higher altitude have lower possibility of dying from heart disease than those closer to sea level, even if they have factors that could increase their risk. \"Residence in mountainous areas seems to have a 'protective effect' from heart disease,\" said Dr Nikos Baibas of the University of Athens. He and his colleagues suspect that the increased exercise from walking up mountainous area gives the heart a good workout and enables it to cope with lower levels of oxygen. Researchers studied the health records and death rates of 1,150 Greeks who lived in three villages near Athen...\n\nQ: How long does the research of the Greeks last?", "options": ["At most 10 years.", "Not mentioned.", "More than 20 years.", "About 15 years."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 967, "question": "The skin which covers the tips of the fingers and thumbs is crossed by numerous ridges arranged in different patterns. These patterns are permanent from birth and remain exactly the same throughout a person's life, even when the skin becomes wrinkled and cracked as a result of old age. Such patterns are never passed on from parents to children, and no one in the world has the same patterns as anyone else. Even identical twins have different sets of fingerprints. As a result, fingerprints offer a most useful and _ way of identifying people. Any ridged part of the hand and the foot may be used as a means of identification, but finger impressions are usually preferred since they can be taken easily and quickly. Fingerprints are classified in the ways: by general shapes and contours , by the f...\n\nQ: The word \"foolproof\" (Line 7, Para. 1) most probably means   _  .", "options": ["that is permanent", "that is acceptable", "that can not go wrong", "that is not foolish"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2296, "question": "Guide dogs are going to be available for the children who are unable to see normally in the UK for the first time, as the age limit is to be removed. The Guide Dogs for the Blind Association is to begin training dogs to help blind people under the age of 16. The association says too many youngsters with impaired eyesight are lacking in independence. They have only a limited social life because of their disability. Giving some of them guide dogs at a younger age is intended to help them to widen their range of activities and to improve their sense of self-confidence and independence. Guide dogs for these teenagers will begin to be provided from next year. There has been an experimental project to test the use of guide dogs with younger people. Charlotte, aged 14, was among the youngest guid...\n\nQ: According to the text, Charlotte's example proves that  _  .", "options": ["it is necessary to carry out the experimental project", "guide dogs can get along well with disabled people", "the association's opinion is not quite right", "youngsters need companions and friends"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3374, "question": "Farmer John and Farmer Bob were neighbors. For more than 30 years, they had been getting along very well. Then their good relationship broke. It began with a small thing, then bitter words, and then weeks of silence. One morning Farmer John woke up to find a stream between the two farms. \"It must be Bob,\" John thought. Then one day there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a carpenter standing at the doorway. \"I'm looking for a few days' work,\" the carpenter said. \"I do have a job for you,\" John said. \"Look across the stream at that farm. That's my neighbor Bob. He dug a stream between the two farms. I want you to build a fence--an 8-foot fence. I don't want to see his place or his face any more. I don't have such a neighbor!\" The carpenter said, \"I think I know what to do, si...\n\nQ: What do you think of the carpenter?", "options": ["Shy.", "Wise.", "Proud.", "Careless."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 581, "question": "Dear Ms Morris, We have come to know of an unfortunate incident you had with our customer service department and we would like to deeply apologize for the inconvenience caused to you by the customer service manager's behavior. We have noted down your complaint (number 797329SA) and would like to let you know that strict action will be taken against the employee. He is a new employee with little experience and so his attitude towards his job was over enthusiastic and he lacked proper judgment. We are by no means excusing his behavior but I would like to request you not to take any legal action against the company as we are very sorry for what happened. To express our appreciation, please accept the offer of free servicing of all products of our company that you own for up to three years. We...\n\nQ: What is Ms Morris's attitude towards the customer service manager?", "options": ["Thankful.", "Dissatisfied.", "Doubtful.", "Worried."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1582, "question": "Zoe, Damacela, 19, didn't have nice clothes when she was young. It wasn't easy for Zoe's hard-working single mother to make ends meet. They moved in and out of homeless shelters. Everything changed for Zoe in grade nine. At that time, she heard about a sewing class at her school. She signed up and couldn't wait to turn her designs into clothes. The color of the first dress she made was white-black strips. Soon the clothes she wore were all made by her. Other girls at school loved her designs too. They asked her if they could buy dresses from her. Zoe sold her first dress for $13. Unfortunately, it cost her $25 to make the dress. \"I had the creativity in designs,\" says Zoe. \"But I really had no idea about business.\" Zoe kept selling the clothes she designed. Her business was booming, and ev...\n\nQ: We can learn that   _  when she was in grade nine.", "options": ["Zoe had no interest in designing clothes", "Zoe seldom wore her self-made clothes", "Zoe didn' t know how to make money", "Zoe attended a business course"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3227, "question": "Global warming is causing more than 300,000 deaths and about $125 billion in economic losses each year, according to a report by the Global Humanitarian Forum, an organization led by Annan, the former United Nations secretary general. The report, to be released Friday, analyzed data and existing studies of health, disaster, population and economic trends. It found that human-influenced climate change was raising the global death rates from illnesses including malnutrition and heat-related health problems. But even before its release, the report drew criticism from some experts on climate and risk, who questioned its methods and conclusions. Along with the deaths, the report said that the lives of 325 million people, primarily in poor countries, were being seriously affected by climate chan...\n\nQ: What is the finding of the Global Humanitarian Forum?", "options": ["Global temperatures affect the rate of economic development.", "Rates of death from illnesses have risen due to global warming.", "Malnutrition has caused serious health problems in poor countries.", "Economic trends have to do with population and natural disasters."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1777, "question": "Dear Santa Claus, My name is Amy. I am 9 years old. I have a problem at school. Can you help me, Santa? Kids laugh at me because of the way I walk and run and talk. I have cerebral palsy. I just want one day when no one laughs at me or makes fun of me. Love, Amy At radio station WJLT in Fort Wayne, Indiana, letters poured in for the Christmas Wish Contest. When Amy's letter arrived at the radio station, manager Lee Tobin read it carefully. He thought it would be good for the people in Fort Wayne to hear about this special third grader and her unusual wish. Mr. Tobin called up the local newspaper. The next day, a picture of Amy and her letter to Santa made the front page of the \"News Sentinel\". The story spread quickly. All across the country, newspapers and radio and television stations re...\n\nQ: The Fort Wayne mayor officially proclaimed Amy Jo Hagadorn Day   _   .", "options": ["to tell how bad teasing can make others feel", "to encourage people to carry their heads high", "to call on the public to treat everyone properly", "to explain how brave Amy was by making her wish"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 980, "question": "NEW DELHI, India (AP)--India is fast becoming a top destination for tourists thanks to a forceful campaign to push the country's Himalayan spas and beaches, officials say. Tourism officials have been crisscrossing the globe as part of the government's \"Incredible India\" campaign launched in 2003. And the results are beginning to show. Tourists traveling to prefix = st1 /Indiahave jumped by nearly 26 percent from last year and the number is expected to cross 3 million this year, said Amitabh Kant, chairman of the India Tourism Development Corp. \"Foreign exchange earnings, too, have shown a nearly 40 percent rise this year,\" Kant told The Associated Press. India's earnings from tourism were $4.3 billion between January and November 2004, compared to $3.1 billion for the same period of 2003. ...\n\nQ: Tourism officials have been crisscrossing the globe to   _  .", "options": ["learn from resorts", "strengthen communication", "draw tourists to India", "enjoy the scenery"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1556, "question": "There have been many great inventions, which have changed the way we live. The first great invention was one that is still very important today---the wheel. This made it easier to carry heavy things to travel long distances. For hundreds of years there were few inventions that have made as much effect as the wheel. There was little unknown land left in the world. People didn't have to explore much any more. They began to work to make life better instead. In the second half of the 19th century many great inventions were made. Among them were the camera, the electric light and the radio. These all became a big part of our life today. The first part of the 20th century saw more great inventions. The helicopter in 1909. Sound movies in 1926. The computer in 1928, and jet planes in 1930. This w...\n\nQ: This passage talks mainly about   _  .", "options": ["how inventions affect people's life", "when electric light was invented", "which country made the first step into space", "why cars were very important"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3343, "question": "People with disabilities make up a large part of the population. It is estimated that over 35 million Americans have physical, mental, or other disabilities. About half of these disabilities are \"developmental\", i.e., they occur before the individual's twenty-second birthday, often from genetic conditions, and are severe enough to affect three or more areas of development, such as mobility, communication, employment, etc. Most other disabilities are considered \"adventitious\", i.e., accidental or caused by outside forces. Prior to the 20th century, only a small percentage of people with disabilities survived for long. Medical treatment for these disabilities was unavailable. Advancements in medicine and social services have created a climate in which people with disabilities can expect to h...\n\nQ: Most disabled people used to die early because   _  .", "options": ["disabilities destroyed major bodily functions", "they were not very well looked after", "medical techniques were not available", "they were too poor to get proper treatment"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2460, "question": "With a good shopping position and the right amount of money , any educated person ought to be able to make a living out of a bookshop . It is not a difficult trade to learn and the large chain-stores can never force the small bookseller out of existence as they have done to the corner shop . But the hours of work are very long-I was only doing a part-time job , but my boss put in a seventy-hour week ,besides regular journeys out of shopping hours to buy books . The real reason why I should not like to be back in the book trade for life , however , is that while I was in it, I lost my love of books . A bookseller cannot always tell the truth about his books , and that gives him a dislike for them . There was a time when I really did love books--loved the sight and smell and feel of them--if...\n\nQ: The author should not like to be back as a bookseller for life because_.", "options": ["he hated his job of selling books", "selling books was only a part-time job", "the books in the shop gave him a dislike", "he was unable to be honest about the books he sold"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2357, "question": "The crowd cheered and cheered. The man with the horn waved and smiled his great smile. \"More! More!\" cried the crowd. And Louis Armstrong took his horn and began to play again. Here he was in England. Now a famous man, he was rich. He knew many important people. Wherever he went, people knew his name. They wanted to hear his music. As he played the sad, slow songs, Louis thought of his home in New Orleans. He lived there as a boy. It was a busy, exciting city. But Louis's family was very poor. He went to work to help his mother. He also went to school. One of Louis's teachers asked him to join the school band. \"This horn is yours until you leave our school,\" his teacher said. Louis's music was jazz and he loved it. He remembered all the music he heard. He didn't learn to read music until h...\n\nQ: Louis went to work when he was   _  .", "options": ["a schoolboy", "a musician", "famous", "a man"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 192, "question": "Boys' schools are the perfect place to teach young men to express their emotions and involve them in activities such as art, dance and music. Far from the traditional image of a culture of aggressive masculinity ,the absence of girls gives boys the chance to develop without pressure to be consistent to a stereotype ,a US study says. Boys at single-sex schools were said to be more likely to get involved in cultural and artistic activities that helped develop their abilities to express their emotions,rather than feeling they had to obey to the\"boy code\"of hiding their emotions to be a\"real man\". The findings of the study are against the received wisdom that boys do better when taught alongside girls. Tony Little,headmaster of Eton,warned that boys were being ignored by the British education ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the characteristic of boys according to Abigail James'report?", "options": ["They enjoy being in charge.", "They act the same to stereotypes.", "They have sharper vision.", "They are violent and sexist."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 830, "question": "Among the many differences between Western and Chinese cultures, table manners are one of the most noticeable differences. Westerners often make mistakes at the table in China or in a Chinese home. In order not to have an embarrassing experience, here are some things to consider next time you are eating with some Chinese. Step1: Keep in mind that food is shared. It is one of the biggest differences between Chinese and Western eating habits. In China a few dishes are placed in the center of a table and shared by all. Also, you should offer thanks when a Chinese host takes food from one of the dishes on the table and places it on your plate. Refusing it would not be polite even if you are full. Step2: Respect the chopsticks. The chopsticks are the single most important tool at a Chinese tabl...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the following are wrong EXCEPT that   _  .", "options": ["you don't have to accept the food a Chinese host places on your plate", "a skewer is also a commonly used tool at a Chinese table", "one can offer his own chopsticks for communal use when there aren't any", "when clinking glasses, the rim of the younger person should be lower than that of the older person"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 431, "question": "Health insurance can be very expensive. Some working people do not make enough money to pay for it. In the US there is a program called Healthy Families. This program offers people health insurance at a low cost. Families are charged about $7.00 a month for every child, and $10.00 for every adult. It costs much less than any other kind of health insurance. Having health insurance is very important. With this insurance, people can see a doctor when they are sick or hurt. The program is not expensive at all, but many people are still not enrolling in it. People say that it still costs too much money. They need all of their money to pay for things like food and rent . It would be great if everyone could have health insurance. People are working hard to come up with ways to make this happen. O...\n\nQ: The aim of the Healthy Families Program is to   _  .", "options": ["help people earn more and pay for the program", "make it free for people to see a doctor", "help more families get health insurance", "help families pay for private health insurance"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 708, "question": "Children grow quickly, especially their feet, but many families cannot buy new shoes each time a child needs them. As a result, about 300 million children around the world go barefoot. Those children risk picking up diseases and parasites from the soil. An American man may have a solution for those barefoot kids -- a shoe that grows with the child. Kenton Lee is the creator of The Shoe That Grows. He explains how the shoe works and how it is able to last so long. \"It grows in three places: the front; it can also grow on the side with Velcro; and on the back with our buckle. It can last up to five years. The bottom is compressed rubber like tire rubber. The top is just high-quality leather.\" The shoe comes in two sizes: small that fits children aged 4 to 9 and large for children aged 9 to 1...\n\nQ: Who is this kind of newly invented shoes intended for?", "options": ["All the teenagers.", "Children aged 4 to 14.", "Middle-aged women in Africa.", "Senior citizens with low income."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1459, "question": "When, after a year of being alone on his island, Robinson Crusoe sees a footprint in the sand, the reader of Robinson Crusoe trembles. Will Crusoe find another human being to end his loneliness? Is the footprint the sign of an enemy? Since 1719, when Daniel Defoe wrote Robinson Crusoe, thousands of people who enjoy English novels have thrilled to this great adventure story. But few know how the story came to be written. Robinson Crusoe was the first English novel. Its birth brought together the misadventures of a Scotch \"failure\" and the untapped imagination of an aging English scribbler. Near the end of the Seventeenth Century, the hot-tempered Alexander Selkirk was charged with bad conduct while in church. Rather than face this charge, he ran away to sea. Several years later, Selkirk fou...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly about_.", "options": ["how Alexander Selkirk was able to survive on the island.", "why people enjoy English novels", "what the footprint in the sand meant", "how Robinson Crusoe came to be written"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2271, "question": "The students in America usually begin high school at the age of 13 or 14. Some leave at the age of 16. But most finish the 4-year high school study. They do not get their first full-time work or begin college studies until they are 17 or 18 years old. The high school day is about 7 hours long. Part of the day is made into classes of about 50 minutes long. The students have lunch in the middle of the day. American students study English, history, math, science, art and languages. Some also learn job skills. They can learn how to use a computer or how to mend a car. Other students may learn by working in an office, a hospital or other places one day a week. Jean Wilton Anderson is 16 years old. She lives with her parents and two younger brothers in Bethesda, Maryland, near Washington D.C. Je...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true?", "options": ["Students in high schools use the word \"like\" very often", "The boy students wear blue jeans as the girls.", "Many high school students go to school in their own cars.", "Boy students wear jeans of larger size because they grow fast"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1785, "question": "Here is some must-know information from a handbook on how people behave in doing business in some countries. In Brazil Brazilians are warm and friendly.They often stand close when talking and it is common for them to touch the person on the shoulder.People often greet each other (particularly women)with light cheek kisses . Schedules tend to be flexible,with business meetings sometimes starting later than planned.But to be safe,be on time.Meals can stretch for hours--there's no such thing as rushing a meal in Brazil.Lunches also can start in the mid to late afternoon.Brazilians are social,preferring face-to-face communication over emails or phone calls. In Singapore Singaporeans shake hands when they meet and often also greet each other with a small,polite bow.Business cards should be offe...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["communication types", "the workplace atmosphere", "customs and social manners", "1iving conditions and standards"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2680, "question": "Tokyo University laboratory has developed a robot that never loses at the game of Rock Paper Scissors. That is because its visual processing abilities and fingers work together faster than any human brain. A video of the undefeated robot has been watched by more than 3 million viewers on YouTube since going online at the end of June. Tokyo University engineering professor Masatoshi Ishikawa has a good-natured response to frustrated human losers who accuse him of essentially creating a robot that cheats. \"It is not cheating. Every one millisecond the image processor decides and recognizes the shape the human hand is going to make. And then the robot can make a winnable shape one millisecond later than a human being. Only one millisecond, but a human cannot see this difference because the hu...\n\nQ: Which section of a website is the text probably taken from?", "options": ["Sports and games.", "Human and society.", "Science and technology.", "Relaxation and entertainment."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2129, "question": "The management and staff are happy to welcome you and will do all they can to make your stay an enjoyable one. We hope you will find the following suggestions and information of use to you. MEAL TIMES Our overnight charge includes a continental-type breakfast. Breakfast: 7:30-9:30 a. m. Lunch: 12:00-2:00 p. m. Afternoon tea: 4:00-5:30 p. m. Dinner: 7:00-9:15 p. m. Meals can be served in rooms at a small extra charge. We regret that owing to staff arrangements, meals cannot be served outside these times. In exceptional circumstances please consult one of our receptionists in advance. Light refreshments, including tea, coffee, biscuits and sandwiches, can be served in rooms between 10:00 a. m. and 11:00 p. m. except during the meal times listed above. Cold drinks are available in the room re...\n\nQ: If you intend to leave the room tomorrow, you may leave at any of the following hours except   _", "options": ["3:00 p. m.", "12:00 a. m.", "10:00 a. m.", "11:00 a. m."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2667, "question": "New York City schoolchildren can't use cellphones at school because of Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg's ban on cellphones in schools. Many parents are opposed to Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg's ban on cellphones in schools by e-mail messages. There was a 13-year-old student who was shot with a gun after school, unable to call his mother for help. There was a high school student robbed three times last year, twice in her school building. There was a girl who got a piece of glass placed in her eye during school and was saved from a possible cornea transplant only because, having disobeyed the cellphone ban, she was able to call her mother and get an operation on time. The ban has been on for years, but it set off a widespread parental outcry only in April, after some headmasters sent home letters r...\n\nQ: According to what the spokesman said, the school might   _  .", "options": ["call off the ban", "continue the ban", "thank the parents", "allow some students to use cellphones at school"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 261, "question": "Is It OK to Snap Your Food? Have you ever taken a snap of a luxurious cake or photographed a juicy steak when you eat in restaurants? You may want to share what you eat with your friends or just post part of your daily life onto the Internet. However, such action may be very annoying to other diners, or even to chefs and restaurant owners. Currently, more and more people begin to consider \" foodstagramming\" as very silly and a bad manner. In many restaurants, diners complain of being blinded by flasher , snapped without their permission and disturbed by people climbing on to chairs for a better angle. Even chefs and restaurant owners are annoyed at food photography. A Michelin-starred chef said, \"It's hard to build a memorable evening when flashes are flying every six minutes.\" At the star...\n\nQ: What did some New York restaurants do about food photography?", "options": ["They started to ban customers from taking photos of their food.", "They had no idea about taking photos for the profits.", "They wanted to talk with some customers.", "They decided to learn from Spain."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2845, "question": "I want to let you know about an event that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Sunday morning. We decided to stop at a local gas station to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as if he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something to drink. However, it was not this that moved me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog lover, I noticed that the dog was a mother and that she had just had some puppies . She was hungry and weak and I felt so bad for her. I knew if she di...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we know that the homeless man was   _  .", "options": ["kind and helpful", "brave and kind", "clever and helpful", "clever and brave"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2786, "question": "There are two factors which determine an individual's intelligence. The first is the sort of brain he is born with. Human brains differ considerably, some being more capable than others. But no matter how good a brain he has to begin with, an individual will have a low order of intelligence unless he has opportunities to learn. So the second factor is what happens to the individual--the sort of environment in which he is reared . If an individual is handicapped environmentally, it is likely that his brain will fail to develop and he will never attain the level of intelligence of which he is capable. The importance of environment in determining an individual's intelligence can be demonstrated by the case history of the identical twins, Peter and Mark X. Being identical, the twins had identi...\n\nQ: The case history of the twins appears to support the conclusion that   _  .", "options": ["individual with identical brains seldom test at same level", "an individual's intelligence is determined only by his environment", "changes of environment produce changes in the structure of the brain", "lack of opportunity blocks the growth of intelligence"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 507, "question": "I am so worried about global warming. We need stop cutting down all of the trees so that they can absorb the carbon dioxide. I think the Kyoto Protocol to stop pollution is a great idea ,and I hope our country will decide to follow it, too.[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/] -- Eli S.,10,Texa People should do all they can to help stop pollution, even if it is something as little as recycling your soda can. Every little thing helps. Maybe schools can put recycling bins in classrooms. Students can bring in all of their cans and bottles and see how many the school can collect. -- Lindsey A.,11, Massachusett[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/.Com] The United States should take action to help stop pollution. Since we are one of the richest countries, we should at least spend a little money to help. -- Aaron z,11,Mass...\n\nQ: Augustine worries that global warming problems will be difficult to solve because  _  .", "options": ["many people think that global warming cannot be stopped", "more and more trees are being cut down", "American government spends little money stopping pollution", "the U.S. refuses to follow the Kyoto Protocol"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1032, "question": "Some kinds of mental skills naturally decrease as people get older. Yet research seems to show that some training can improve such skills. A recently published study also appears to demonstrate that the good effects of training can last for many years after that training has ended. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University in Maryland wanted to learn how long memory and thinking skills would last in older people who trained to keep them. The people were part of the ten-year research project. They were taught methods meant to improve their memory, thinking and ability to perform everyday tasks. More than 2,800 volunteered for the study called ACTIVE - short for Advanced (Cognitive) Training for Independent and Vital Elderly. Most studied when they were more than 70 years old. The volunteers t...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Mental Training Helped Elderly Stay Sharp for Years", "How to improve our mental health", "Four groups of old people were trained mentally.", "The result of a ten-year research"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 766, "question": "\"To be or not to be.\" Outside the Bible, these six words are the most famous in all the literature of the world. They were spoken by Hamlet when he was thinking aloud, and they are the most famous words in Shakespeare because Hamlet was speaking not only for himself but also for every thinking man and woman. To be or not to be, to live or not to live, to live richly and abundantly, or to live dully and meanly. A philosopher once wanted to know whether he was alive or not, which is a good question for everyone to put to himself occasionally. He answered it by saying: \"I think, therefore I am.\" But the best definition of existence I ever saw was one written by another philosopher who said: \"To be is to be in relations.\" If this is true, then the more relations a living thing has, the more it...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["To be is to be in relations.", "I think, therefore I am.", "To be or not to be, that is a question.", "A man dies as often as he loses a friend."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1116, "question": "\"Migrant workers\" is a familiar term for 17-year-old Shi Jian. Her father and uncle often talk about the problems surrounding this group of people. However, Shi cares more about the children of these migrant workers. Last year Shi's housekeeper's daughter had to give up her schooling in Beijing because she would not be allowed to sit the national college entrance exam. She was forced to continue her high school education in her hometown in Sichuan Province. Shi thinks the current law is unfair for migrant workers' children, as it prevents them from studying at public schools, unless their parents pay huge sums. So, Shi decided to do a survey of migrant workers so that she could find some solutions to help solve the problem. In the last six months Shi spoke to 186 migrant workers in Beijing...\n\nQ: What drove Shi to do the survey of migrant workers?", "options": ["Her curiosity about migrant workers' lives", "She was asked to do a survey of migrant workers as part of a school project.", "Her housekeeper's daughter was forced to move to her hometown to continue studying.", "She wanted to draw people's attention and become famous"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2886, "question": "Skateboarding has become one of several non-traditional activities that PE teachers around America are introducing to inspire kids to exercise regularly. Some PE classes feature in-line skating, yoga, and even rock climbing. Experts have called those types of activities \"the new PE\". Such activities are part of a larger effort to help kids develop lifelong fitness habits and to keep them from becoming overweight. Now, 9 million U.S. children and teens are overweight. Obesity can lead to health problems such as diabetes and heart disease later in life. \"Our children and youth are becoming unhealthy and obese,\" says Johnson. \"Skateboarding is a great activity that keeps kids doing physical movement and gives them new skills and interest.\" Some schools don't allow skateboarding because they s...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The dangerous PE", "Skills of skateboarding.", "The new PE.", "The change of PE."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 637, "question": "As people have accurately observed,smiles are absent from early photographs. In 1852,for instance,a girl sat for her Daguerrotype,her head slightly turned,giving the camera an unsmiling look. She is preserved forever as a very serious girl indeed. Charles Darwin,a loving and playful parent,looks frozen in photographs. Why did our ancestors,from unknown sitters for family portraits to the great and famous,because so sad in front of the camera? The severity is everywhere in Victorian photographs. However,you don't have to look very long at these unsmiling old photos to see how incomplete the seemingly obvious answer is-that they are freezing their faces in order to keep still for the long exposure times. In Julia Margaret Cameron's Portrait of Tennyson,the poet dreams,his face a shadowed mas...\n\nQ: The author thinks early people look frozen in old photos because  _  .", "options": ["they lived in a traditional society", "they had to stay still for a long time", "they regarded photography important", "they held negative views about painting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2501, "question": "Alaska's Arctic lakes now freeze later and melt earlier in the year than in 1950,leaving them easy to suffer water loss from evaporation and possibly adding to local warming,a new study finds.The winter ice season near Barrow,Alaska,is shorter than in 1950,researchers reported Jan.30 in the journal The Cryosphere. Lake ice is also thinner each winter.The scientists surveyed 402 lakes on the North Slope,where permafrost (permanently frozen ground)and shallow lakes dominate the areA. In 2011,the lake ice was 38 percent thinner than in 1950,and 22 percent fewer lakes froze through to their bottoms. \"When we saw the actual numbers we were shocked at how dramatic the change has been,\"lead study author Cristina Surdu,of the University of Waterloo in Canada,said in a statement.Surdu and her co-au...\n\nQ: According to the text,the great changes of Alaska's Arctic lakes   _  .", "options": ["are totally beyond Surdu's expectations", "are completely within Surdu's expectations", "come as no surprise to Surdu and her co-authors", "come as a great excitement to Surdu"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2452, "question": "Norway tops the list of countries that offers the best social policies for people over 60. Afghanistan is rated the worst. The rankings appear in the new Global Age Watch Index. Help Age International published the index of 96 countries that are home to 790-million people 60 and older. Chief Executive Officer Toby Porter said, \"For too long, older people have been excluded from international and national development planning. We have a world which is ageing fast. And what the index does is to compare and rank countries from best to worst countries in the world to grow old,\" he said. The Global Age Watch Index rates countries in four categories. \"Health, income, what we call capability - ability to carry on contributing employment. And then the final one about enabling environment - what do...\n\nQ: What is the focus on the report of this year?", "options": ["Pension", "Capability", "Employment", "Health"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1163, "question": "What's A Real Friend? You can have the same neighbors for years. You love them or you think you love them. And you hope that they love you. But do you ever really understand them? Charlie Kemp and his family lived next door to me for 15 years. We were good friends all the time. I enjoy friendship. I think it's the best thing in the world. And friendship with the Kemps was easy because they seemed to welcome it. They were interesting and clever people. Their house caught fire twice, and twice the whole family slept in mine. They are always losing things like money, keys and watches. Pictures fell off the walls, the children fell out of bed ... I was their neighbor and their friend. Life was always interesting, never dull. Best of all, I liked the whole family. One day, I lit a fire in the g...\n\nQ: According to the passage,   _  .", "options": ["Charlie Kemp is the author's neighbor and his real good friend", "Charlie Kemp is the author's neighbor but not his real good friend", "Charlie Kemp treats the author as his real good friend", "the author doesn't treat Charlie Kemp as his real good friend"], "answer": 1}]